{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "я", "answer": "есть" },
    { "prompt": "ты", "answer": "есть" },
    { "prompt": "он", "answer": "есть" },
    { "prompt": "она", "answer": "есть" },
    { "prompt": "оно", "answer": "есть" },
    { "prompt": "есть", "answer": "я/ты/он/она/оно" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "я", "answer": "имею" },
    { "prompt": "ты", "answer": "имеешь" },
    { "prompt": "он", "answer": "имеет" },
    { "prompt": "она", "answer": "имеет" },
    { "prompt": "мы", "answer": "имеем" },
    { "prompt": "вы", "answer": "имеете" },
    { "prompt": "они", "answer": "имеют" },
    { "prompt": "имею", "answer": "я" },
    { "prompt": "имеешь", "answer": "ты" },
    { "prompt": "имеет", "answer": "он/она" },
    { "prompt": "имеем", "answer": "мы" },
    { "prompt": "имеете", "answer": "вы" },
    { "prompt": "имеют", "answer": "они" }
  ]
}
